I've got news on the human brain
organoids you know the organoids those
little human brains that we grew in jars
that grow eyes capable of seeing and
processing light you know the ones that
scientists made play Pong and did better
than Ai and is currently being used to
develop bioom computers well the issue
of vascularization may be pretty close
to being solved when they grow for too
long because they aren't attached to a
functional heart they end up becoming
hypoxic some scientists try to solve
that by placing it inside a mouse brain
and it actually made connections and
worked while considering they're able to
grow it next to a decapitated Mouse and
it took over the muscles scientists
figure it could probably work together
so we can actually make larger more
complex brain structures by growing the
different structures of the brain
separately and then fusing them together
with this we're able to make more
complex brains and now we're making them
mentally ill with Fusion they're
actually able to grow structures that
they weren't able to grow initially with
the brain organoids and that includes
micral cells from here we may be able to
understand different mental illnesses as
well as things like Alzheimer's and
plaque disorders the idea of having a
brain organoid that's mentally ill is a
little bit concerning when we're talking
about bioom computers I imagine they
would always become mentally ill
although what I'm more excited about is
being able to grow different brain
structures infusing it into live brains
that have become damaged by tvis or
Strokes although the ability for them to
be sentient is a little bit concerning
when we're talking about implanting them
into other people's brains because how
much of that intelligence is being
transferred and will that just
incorporate itself into the brain
structures and become part of your
Consciousness I don't know but I'm at
least happy that I have